<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Incident Reporting App</string>
    <string name="title_activity_register">RegisterActivity</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="open_drawer">open_drawer</string>
    <string name="drawer_closed">drawer_closed</string>
    <string name="long_hold_images">Long press the button to take picture with the camera.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="long_hold_video">Long press the button to record video.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms">Terms_Activity</string>
    <string name="MAP_API_KEY">AIzaSyDtwI2crDNZUEfNhLT8qR055IhSyOJn98M</string>
    <string name="terms">
        Please read the following User Terms and Conditions ("Terms") carefully before using the Incident Reporting Application ("the Application").&#xA;\n\n
        (i) Incident Reporting Application a stores user credentials namely the email, names,
    contact for better user experience.&#xA; \n\n

(ii) This application also keeps track of the user reports submitted storing the image(s) path(s), video path
    also other text input entries.&#xA;\n\n

(iii) This application takes a back up of the user video supplied in the email attachment.&#xA;\n\n

(iv) The application request the read and write permissions of the external storage.&#xA;\n\n

(v) No image data is stored by the application.&#xA;\n\n

(vi) Whiz Studios is not responsible and does not keep track of any modifications done by the user
    on the mail body outside the application and also not responsible for the information submitted.&#xA;\n\n

(vii) The user should note that the supplied information goes to the gmail account of Uganda Police.&#xA;\n\n

(viii) The user whom supplied a report may or may not be contacted by police for further investigations.&#xA;\n\n

(ix) User backed information may be used by police on request.&#xA;\n\n

    By counting to use the application, means that the user agrees to the above terms.&#xA;\n\n

    For a crime free Uganda.
    </string>
    <string name="user_policy">
        User Policy of the Incident Reporting Application:&#xA;\n\n

        Privacy Policy: User information is kept secret from third party access and secure however
        it could be share to the police on request for further investigations.&#xA;\n\n

Incident Reporting Guidelines: Pornographic,
        obscene and other offensive content is highly prohibited and if used could lead to a legal action.&#xA;\n\n

Non-Retaliation Policy: This ensures that users can report incidents without fear of
        retaliation and users should report information in good faith without any bias.&#xA;\n\n

Confidentiality Policy: Collected information from the users specifically the video, names, location, and the email, are kept secure in a remote storage
        and only the information relating to incidents could be shared on request for further investigations.&#xA;\n\n

User Conduct Policy: As stated already that abuse of the user policy could call for legal actions in case the user submits misleading information,
        pornographic or any other form of inhumane information.&#xA;\n\n

Response and Resolution Policy: The developers of this application are not responsible for the responses you receive after sending the information to the police.&#xA;
Data Retention Policy: Data back-ups are stored for a given time 2-4 years for a better experience.&#xA;\n\n
</string>
    <string name="view_terms">Check box to accept the terms of using this application. Click here to view terms.</string>
</resources>